Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004 UA.27.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Mandl, Michael J. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Financial Services
- Manikam, Rajah B. (Box 37)
- Manly, Jethro O. (Box 37)
- Mann, Charles E. (Box 37)
- Mann, Charles E. (Box 134)
- Mann, Charles E. (Box 152)
- Mann, Everett J. (Box 85)
- Mann, Everett James (Box 37)
- Mann, Everett James (Box 134)
- Mann, Glenn E. (Ted) (Box 134)
- Mann, Glenn E. (Ted) (Box 152)
- Mann, Glenn E. (Ted) (Box 37)
- Mann, W. Joseph (Box 134)
- Mann, W. Joseph (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Continuing Education; Divinity School
- Manry, James C. (Box 37)
- Manry, James C. (Box 134)
- Manschreck, Clyde L. (Box 37)
- Manschreck, Clyde L. (Box 134)
- Mansergh, Nicholas (Box 37)
- Manton, Kenneth G. (Box 134)
- Manton, Kenneth G. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Community and Family Medicine, Before 1993
- Manton, Kenneth G. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Community and Family Medicine, 1993
- Manton, Kenneth G. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Community and Family Medicine, 1994-
- Manton, Kenneth G. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Community and Family Medicine, 2001
- Marberry, J.O. (Box 37)
- March, John S. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Child and Adol. Psychiatry
- Marchase, Richard B. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Research; Anatomy
- Marchuk, Douglas A. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Genetics
- Margolis, George (Box 37)
- Margolis, George (Box 134)
- Margolis, George (Box 152)
- Marinos, Peter N. (Box 134)
- Marinos, Peter N. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Graduate Studies; Electrial Engineering
- Mario, Ernest, Trustee (Box 117)
- Mark, Alan Francis (Box 37)
- Mark, Daniel (Box 85)
- Markee, Joseph E. (Box 37)
- Markee, Joseph E. (Box 134)
- Markert, M. Louise (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Allergy and Immunology; Pediatrics
- Markham, Charles Blackwell (Box 37)
- Markham, Charles Blackwell (Box 152)
- Markley, Robert F. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Corporate/Foundation Relations; Research Administration
- Markman, Sydney (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, retired Aug. 31, 1981
- Markman, Sydney (Box 37)
- Markman, Sydney (Box 134)
- Marks, Jeffrey R., 2001 (Box 85)
- Marks, Lawrence (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiation Oncology, 1999
- Marler, George Eric (Box 85)
- Marney, Carlyle (Box 37)
- Marney, Carlyle (Box 134)
- Marney, Carlyle (Box 152)
- Marr, Thomas Franklin, Trustee (Box 117)
- Marsden, George M. (Box 85)
- Marsden, George M. (Box 134)
- Marsh, Gail R. (Box 134)
- Marsh, Gail R. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Psychology; Psychology
- Marsh, Robert Mortimer (Box 37)
- Marshall, E. C. (Box 134)
- Marshall, E. C. [Duke Endowment Trustee] (Box 117)
- Marshall, Lynn La Due (Box 85)
- Marshall, Norman (Box 85)
- Marshall, Peter (Box 37)
- Marshall, Peter (Box 134)
- Marshall, Robert C. (Box 85)
- Marshall, Roger (Box 37)
- Marshall, Roger (Box 134)
- Marshall, Roger (Box 152)
- Marshall, Roger L. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, Secretary of the University eff. July 1, 1986
- Marshall, William H. (Box 37)
- Marshall, William H. (Box 134)
- Marshall, William H. (Box 152)
- Martin, Abram V., Jr. (Box 85)
- Martin, Anne L. (Box 85)
- Martin, Dale B. (Box 85)
- Martin, Dale B. (Box 135)
- Martin, David Vance (Box 135)
- Martin, David Vance (Box 85)
- Martin, Donald S. (Box 85)
- Martin, Donald S. (Box 152)
- Martin, Donald Stover (Box 37)
- Martin, Jean (Box 85)
- Martin, Joseph B., III (Box 85)
- Martin, Joseph B., III (Box 135)
- Martin, Mrs. John H. (Elsie Wilson) (Box 85)
- Martin, Paul (Box 85)
- Martin, Ruth (Box 85)
- Martin, Ruth (Box 135)
- Martin, Ruth (Box 152)
- Martin, Samuel P. (Box 85)
- Martin, Samuel P. (Box 135)
- Martin, Shirley (Box 85)
- Martin, Willard Edgar, Jr. (Box 85)
- Martin, Willard Edgar, Jr. (Box 135)
- Martin, William Francis (Box 85)
- Martin, William Francis (Box 135)
- Martin, William Francis (Box 152)
- Martinez, Salutario (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Imaging; Radiology
- Mason, Robert (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Orthodontics; Surgery
- Mass, Peter (Box 85)
- Massanari, Ronald L. (Box 85)
- Massanari, Ronald L. (Box 152)
- Massanari, Ronald L. (Box 135)
- Massengill, Raymond (Box 37)
- Massey, Edward Wayne (Box 85)
- Massey, Marilyn Chapin (Box 37)
- Massoud, Hisham Z. (Box 85)
- Matchar, David B. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: General Medicine; Center for Health Policy Research and Education
- Matheson, C. A. (Box 152)
- Matheson, C.R. (Box 135)
- Matheson, C.R. (Box 85)
- Mathew, Roy T. (Box 85)
- Mathews, Donald C. (Box 85)
- Mathews, George, Jr. (Box 85)
- Matthews, L. T. (Box 135)
- Matlock, Jack F., Jr. (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; U.S. Ambassador to the U.S.S.R.
- Matte, Ignacio Elanco (Box 85)
- Matthew, William D. (Box 85)
- Matthews, L. T. (Box 85)
- Matthews, Martha (Box 85)
- Matthews, Minetta (Box 37)
- Matthews, Minetta (Box 135)
- Matthias, Anne Powell (Mrs. Robert C.) (Box 85)
- Matthias, Anne Powell (Mrs. Robert C.) (Box 135)
- Mattingly, Capitola (Box 37)
- Mattingly, Capitola (Box 85)
- Mattingly, Capitola (Box 135)
- Mau, James (Box 85)
- Mau, James (Box 135)
- Maug, Ernst (Box 85)
- Maughan, William (Box 37)
- Maughan, William (Box 85)
- Maughan, William (Box 135)
- Mauskopf, Seymour (Box 135)
- Mauskopf, Seymour (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Graduate Studies; History
- Maves, David Walter (Box 135)
- Maves, David Walter (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Music, 1972-
- Maxfield, Joseph Pease (Box 85)
- Maxson, Wayne S. (Box 37)
- Maxwell, Richard C. (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law, retired Feb. 24, 1989
- Maxwell, Richard C. (Box 135)
- Maxwell, William Cary (Box 37)
- Maxwell, William Cary (Box 135)
- Maxwell, William Cary (Box 152)
- May, Carolyn (Box 135)
- May, Carolyn, 1980 (Box 85)
- May, David E. (Box 85)
- May, David E. (Box 152)
- May, David E. (Box 135)
- May, George (Box 85)
- May, George (Box 135)
- Mayer, Frederick (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Inst. of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs
- Mayer, Frederick (Box 85)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Inst. of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 2001
- Mayer, Robert Andrews (Box 135)
- Mayer, Robert Andrews, d. 8/1/1969, Trustee (Box 117)
- Mayesky, Mary E. (Box 37)
- Mayfield, Demmie G. (Box 86)
- Mayfield, Henry D. (Box 86)
- Mayfield, Henry D. (Box 135)
- Mayfield, Henry D. (Box 152)
- Mayfield, Marie Marcia (Box 86)
- Maynard, Hubbard D. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, retired, 8-31-85
- Maynard, Hubbard D. (Box 135)
- Mayo, Henry Bertram (Box 37)
- Mazumdar, Sucheta (Box 86)
- Mazzola, Joseph (Box 86)
- McAdams, Page (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiology, 1998
- McAlister, Florence (Box 86)
- McAlister, Joe (Box 86)
- McAuley, Gloria M. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Employee Services; Human Resources
- McAuliffe, Johanna (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Drama Dept.
- McBride, Colleen (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Comm. and Family Medicine
- McBryde, Angus Murdoch (Box 38)
- McBryde, Angus Murdoch (Box 135)
- McBryde, Angus Murdoch (Box 152)
- McBryde, Gerald W. (Box 38)
- McBryde, Gerald W. (Box 135)
- McBryde, John M., Jr. (Box 86)
- McBryde, John M., Jr. (Box 135)
- McBryde, John M., Jr. (Box 152)
- McCall, Adeline (Box 38)
- McCall, Adeline (Box 86)
- McCall, Adeline (Box 135)
- McCann, John (Box 135)
- McCann, John (Box 86)
- McCann, Richard L. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Gen and Thoracic Surgery
- McCants, Thomas (Box 86)
- McCardle, Kevin F. (Box 86)
- McCarroll, Earl (Box 86)
- McCarthy, Gregory (Box 86)
- McCarty, Gale A. (Box 38)
- McCarty, Kenneth S., Sr. (Box 86)
- McCarty, Kenneth S., Sr. (Box 135)
- McCarty, Kenneth, Jr. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology; Medicine
- McCaughan, Ralph L. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: University Counsel for Development - Office of the University Counsel
- McCauley, C. Edward (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Duke Hospital, Associate Director, 1969-71
- McCauley, C. Edward (Box 135)
- McClain, Joseph A., Jr. (Box 38)
- McClain, Joseph A., Jr. (Box 135)
- McClay, David R. (Box 86)
- McClay, David R. (Box 135)
- McClellan, John (Box 86)
- McCloy, Shelby T. (Box 86)
- McCloy, Shelby Thomas (Box 38)
- McClure, Wallace (Box 38)
- McClure, Wallace (Box 86)
- McClure, Wallace (Box 135)
- McCollough, Thomas Elmore (Box 135)
- McCollough, Thomas Elmore (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Religion, pre-1995
- McCollough, Thomas Elmore (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Religion, 1995-
- McCollum, David E. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Orthopaedic Surgery; Surgery
- McCollum, Donald E. (Box 135)
- McColm, Mary (Box 86)
- McCombs, Arthur A. (Box 86)
- McCombs, Arthur A. (Box 135)
- McConahay, John B. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1976-77
- McConahay, John B. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1978-94
- McConahay, John B. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Institute of Policy Sciences and Public Affairs, 1995-98
- McConville, Robert H., Jr. (Box 86)
- McCormack, William Charles (Box 86)
- McCormick, Claudia (Box 86)
- McCormick, John C. (Box 86)
- McCracken, Maude (Box 86)
- McCrea, Alice (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiation Therapy
- McCrea, Alice (Box 135)
- McCrory, Douglas C. (Box 86)
- McCue, Betty F. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, 1964-
- McCue, Betty F. (Box 135)
- McCuen, Brooks W. II (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Opatamology
- McCulloch, T. L. (Box 86)
- McCurdy, Linda M. (Box 86)
- McCutcheon, Frederick Harold (Box 86)
- McCutcheon, Frederick Harold (Box 135)
- McDermott, Malcolm (Box 38)
- McDermott, Malcolm (Box 152)
- McDonald, Alexander D. (Box 86)
- McDonald, Alexander Donald (Box 38)
- McDonald, Eugene J. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Executive Vice President and University Counsel
- McDonald, Eugene J. (Box 135)
- McDonald, Marie (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Med Genetics; Peds.
- McDonald, Patrick H (Box 135)
- McDonald, Patrick H., Sr. (Box 86)
- McDonnell, Donald (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pharmacology and Cell Biology
- McDonnell, Thomas E. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: N.R.O.T.C.
- McDougall, William (Box 38)
- McDougall, William (Box 86)
- McDougall, William (Box 152)
- McElhaney, Harold (Box 86)
- McElhaney, James H. (Box 86)
- McElhaney, James W. (Box 86)
- McElroy, Marjorie B. (Box 86)
- McElveen, John T., Jr. (Box 86)
- McEvoy, Joseph (Box 86)
- McFalls, Frederick Dunham (Box 86)
- McFarland, James A. (Box 86)
- McFeaters, C.P. (Box 135)
- McFeaters, C.P. (Box 38)
- McGee, John S. (Box 86)
- McGee, John S. (Box 135)
- McGee, Mike (Box 86)
- McGhee, George C. (Box 135)
- McGhee, George C. (Box 152)
- McGhee, George C., Trustee (Box 117)
- McGinty, Bernard (Box 135)
- McGinty, Bernard (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Center Financial Management
- McGough, William E. (Box 135)
- McGough, William E. (Box 38)
- McGough, William E. (Box 86)
- McGovern, Francis (Box 86)
- McGown, Linda B. (Box 86)
- McGrath, Daniel (Box 38)
- McGrath, Daniel F. (Box 86)
- McGrath, Daniel F. (Box 135)
- McGrath, Diane (Box 38)
- McGuire, Betty (Box 86)
- McGuire, Betty (Box 135)
- McHeyzer-Williams, Michael G. (Box 86)
- McHugh, Gelolo, 2 folders (Box 38)
- McHugh, Gelolo (Box 135)
- McHugh, Gelolo (Box 152)
- McHugh, Gelolo (Box 86)
- McIlrath, Leo (Box 38)
- McIntosh, Henry (Box 38)
- McIntosh, Henry (Box 86)
- McIntosh, Henry (Box 135)
- McIntosh, Thomas (Box 86)
- McKay, Martha (Box 38)
- McKay, Martha (Box 135)
- McKean, Margaret A. (Box 86)
- McKean, Margaret A. (Box 135)
- McKeel, James T., Jr. (Box 86)
- McKenzie, Lionel (Box 86)
- McKinney, John Clifford (Box 38)
- McKinney, John Clifford (Box 135)
- McKinney, Ross E. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Infectious Diseases, Pediatrics
- McKiver, Willard (Box 86)
- McKiver, Willard (Box 135)
- McLachlan, Helen (Box 86)
- McLachlan, Helen (Box 135)
- McLarin, Kim (Box 113)
- McLarty, Furman Gordon (Box 38)
- McLarty, Furman Gordon (Box 135)
- McLarty, Furman Gordon (Box 152)
- McLawhorn, Ruby (Box 86)
- McLean, Edward (Box 38)
- McLelland, Robert (Box 38)
- McLelland, Robert (Box 86)
- McLendon, Jonathon C. (Box 86)
- McLeod, Michael E. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Gastroenterology; Medicine
- McLeod, Robert M. (Box 86)
- McLeod, Robert M. (Box 135)
- McLeod, Robert Melvin (Box 38)
- McLoyd, Vonnie C. (Box 86)
- McMahon, Alex (Box 135)
- McMahon, Alex, Trustee (Box 117)
- McMahon, John Alexander (Box 86)
- McMahon, Samuel M. (Box 86)
- McManus, Mary I. (Box 38)
- McManus, Thomas J. (Box 86)
- McMatton, Timothy (Box 86)
- McMurray, Thomas J. (Box 38)
- McNamara, James O., Sr. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurology; Pharmacology
- McNeill, John Thomas (Box 86)
- McNeill, John Thomas (Box 135)
- McNurlen, Lewis J. (Box 86)
- McNurlen, Lewis J. (Box 135)
- McPhail, Andrew T. (Box 86)
- McPhail, Andrew T. (Box 135)
- McPherson, Harry T. (Box 152)
- McPherson, Harry T. (Box 86)
- McPherson, Harry T. (Box 135)
- Meade, Mary E. (Box 39)
- Meador, Keith G. (Box 86)
- Means, Anthony R. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pharmacology; Molecular Cancer Biology Dept. in Cancer Center
- Meck, Warren H. (Box 86)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychology - Experimental
- Medina, Miguel A. (Box 87)
- Meeks, M. Douglas (Box 87)
- Meeks, M. Douglas (Box 135)
- Meeks, M. Douglas (Box 153)
- Meier, Otto, Jr. (Box 39)
- Meier, Otto, Jr. (Box 135)
- Meier, Otto, Jr. (Box 153)
- Meiller, Joan (Box 39)
- Meiller, Joan (Box 135)
- Meira, Joao Alves (Box 39)
- Melges, Frederick Towne (Box 39)
- Melges, Frederick Towne (Box 135)
- Melion, Walter S. (Box 39)
- Meliones, Jon N. (Box 87)
- Mellown, Elgin Wendell, Jr. (Box 87)
- Melosh, Robert J. (Box 87)
- Melosh, Robert J. (Box 135)
- Mendell, Lorne (Box 39)
- Mendell, Nancy Role (Box 87)
- Mendoza, Enrique (Box 87)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Economics, 2001
- Menefee, E.E. "Lige" (Box 39)
- Menefee, EE (Box 153)
- Mengel, Charles E. (Box 39)
- Mengel, Charles E. (Box 87)
- Mengel, Charles E. (Box 153)
- Menkin, Valy (Box 39)
- Mennini, Louis (Box 39)
- Mennini, Louis (Box 135)
- Mennini, Louis (Box 153)
- Menzel, Daniel B. (Box 39)
- Menzel, Daniel B. (Box 135)
- Menzies, Robert J. (Box 39)
- Meredith, Dennis (Box 87)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Office of Research Communications
- Meredith, Jill (Box 87)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Curator
- Meriam, James Lathrop (Box 39)
- Meriam, James Lathrop (Box 87)
- Meriam, James Lathrop (Box 153)
- Meriam, James Lathrop (Box 135)
- Mericle, Mary Fontaine (Box 39)
- Merritt, Gertrude (Box 87)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Faculty of the Arts and Sciences
- Metcalf, Zeno Payne (Box 39)
- Metzgar, Richard S. (Box 153)
- Metzgar, Richard S. (Box 87)
- Metzgar, Richard S. (Box 135)
- Metzloff, Thomas B. (Box 87)
- Meurer, Mike (Box 87)
- Meurer, Mike (Box 135)
- Meyer, Francis P. (Box 87)
- Meyer, Horst (Box 153)
- Meyer, Horst (Box 87)
- Meyers, Carol (Box 87)
- Meyers, Carol (Box 135)
- Meyers, Edward (Box 39)
- Meyers, Eric (Box 135)
- Meyers, Eric M. (Box 153)
- Meyers, Eric M. (Box 87)
- Meyers, Francis P. (Box 135)
- Meyer, Horst (Box 135)
- Meyers, William C. (Box 87)
- Meyvaert, Paul (Box 39)
- Mezzatesta, Michael P. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Duke University Museum of Art
- Mezzatesta, Michael P. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Duke University Museum of Art, 1993-
- Mezzatesta, Michael P. (Box 135)
- Michalak, Victor (Box 39)
- Michalak, Victor (Box 136)
- Michener, J. Lloyd (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Family Medicine, 1994-
- Michlin, Michael (Box 39)
- Mickey, H. C. (Box 88)
- Mickey, H. C. (Box 136)
- Mickey, Paul A. (Box 88)
- Mickey, Paul A. (Box 136)
- Mickiewicz, Ellen (Box 88)
- Mickle, Thomas P. (Box 88)
- Miers, Ed (Box 153)
- Miglerese, Sam (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Community Affairs
- Mignolo, Walter (Box 88)
- Miksis, Michael John (Box 39)
- Milam, D.F. (Box 39)
- Milbrath, Lester (Box 39)
- Mildram, Robert C. (Box 39)
- Miles, Edward Roy Cecil (Box 39)
- Miles, Edward Roy Cecil (Box 136)
- Miles, Edward Roy Cecil (Box 153)
- Mill, (Rev.) William Robert (Box 136)
- Mill, (Rev.) William Robert (Box 153)
- Mill, W. Robert (Box 39)
- Miller, Ben N. (Box 153)
- Miller, Ben N., Trustee (Box 117)
- Miller, Charles Henderson (Box 88)
- Miller, Christine (Box 39)
- Miller, David L. (Box 88)
- Miller, Donald T. (Box 39)
- Miller, Gustavus (Box 136)
- Miller, Gustavus H. (Box 88)
- Miller, Henry K., Jr. (Box 39)
- Miller, John Noel (Box 39)
- Miller, Joseph (Box 39)
- Miller, Justin (Box 39)
- Miller, Justin (Box 136)
- Miller, Kay (Box 136)
- Miller, Kay (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Office of University Relations; Medical Center Public Relations
- Miller, Lawrence J. (Box 88)
- Miller, Lawrence J. (Box 136)
- Miller, Lowell Stephen (Box 39)
- Miller, Martin (Box 39)
- Miller, Martin A. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: History; Eastern European/Soviet Studies
- Miller, Maude McCracken (Box 39)
- Miller, Robert W. (Box 39)
- Miller, William James (Box 39)
- Miller, William Jones (Box 136)
- Miller, Ylana (Box 88)
- Mills, Elliot (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Physiology, Pharmacology
- Mimms, Christine (Box 39)
- Mimms, Christine (Box 88)
- Mims, Edwin (Box 39)
- Mims, Edwin (Box 153)
- Minah, Theodore W. (Box 39)
- Minah, Theodore W. (Box 88)
- Minah, Theodore W. (Box 136)
- Minnick, Carlton, P., Trustee 1989- (Box 117)
- Minniear, Wilma A. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, retired 5-1-84
- Minniear, Wilma A. (Box 136)
- Miralles, Diego (Box 88)
- Miraus, Earl (Box 153)
- Mishler, Brent (Box 88)
- Mitcham, C. L. (Box 88)
- Mitcham, C.L. (Box 39)
- Mitchell, Fannie Y. (Box 39)
- Mitchell, Fannie Y. (Box 88)
- Mitchell, Frank Kirby (Box 39)
- Mitchell, Jo Anne (Box 39)
- Mitchell, Thomas Greenfield (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Microbiology and Immunology; Clinical Mycology Laboratory
- Mitchell, Will (Box 88)
- Mitchell, William J. (Box 88)
- Mitchum, C. L. (Box 136)
- Mobley, Mark A. (Box 39)
- Mock, Geoffrey, 2001 (Box 88)
- Modrich, Paul L. (Box 88)
- Moeller, Robert C. (Box 88)
- Moeller, Robert C. (Box 153)
- Moi, Toril (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Literature Program
- Moize, Vivian (Box 39)
- Molina, Alexander W. (Box 39)
- Molter, Jeffrey L. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Center News Office
- Moltmann, D. Jurgen (Box 39)
- Moltmann, D. Jurgen (Box 88)
- Moltmann, D. Jurgen (Box 136)
- Mommaerts, Wilfred F. M. H. (Box 88)
- Moneta, Larry (Box 88)
- Monroe, Gary S. (Box 39)
- Monsman, Gerald (Box 39)
- Monsman, Gerald C. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English Dept., 31533
- Montana, Gustavo S. (Box 88)
- Moody, James (Box 136)
- Moody, James (Box 153)
- Moody, James D. (Box 88)
- Moon, Bruce E. (Box 39)
- Moon, Michael (Box 88)
- Moon, Richard E. (Box 88)
- Moon, Richard E. (Box 88)
- Moore, Ann Lee S. (Box 39)
- Moore, Charles A. (Box 88)
- Moore, Donald T. (Box 88)
- Moore, James (Box 39)
- Moore, John Meredith (Box 88)
- Moore, John W. (Box 153)
- Moore, John W. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Physiology, 1-1-90
- Moore, John W. (Box 136)
- Moore, Joseph O. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Hematology and Medical Oncology
- Moore, Lawrence C. (Box 88)
- Moore, Marian (Box 136)
- Moore, Michael, 1992-93 (Box 88)
- Moore, William H. (Box 88)
- Moorman, Christine (Box 88)
- Moorman, Claude T. III (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sports Medicine
- Moosa, Ebrahim (Box 88)
- Moosa, Ebrahim (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Religion, 2001
- Mordon, Mary Jane (Box 88)
- Mordecai, Samuel Fox (Box 88)
- Mordon, Mary Jane (Box 136)
- Mordon, Mary Jane (Box 153)
- Moreiras, Alberto (Box 88)
- Morey, Richard C. (Box 39)
- Morgan, Carlisle Lee, Jr. (Box 39)
- Morgan, George Allen, Jr. (Box 88)
- Morgan, George Allen, Jr. (Box 136)
- Morgan, Henry (Box 88)
- Morgan, Henry (Box 136)
- Morgan, J. E. (Box 88)
- Morgan, J. E. (Box 136)
- Morgan, Philip (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sociology Dept.
- Morgan, Ruby (Box 88)
- Morgan, Ruby (Box 136)
- Morgenstern, Scott (Box 88)
- Morris, Kenneth C. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Health System, Financial Officer
- Morris, Madeline (Box 88)
- Morris, Mary Ann (Box 88)
- Morrison, Ashton Byrom (Box 88)
- Morrison, Ashton Byrom (Box 136)
- Morrison, Ashton Byrom (Box 153)
- Morrison, Clarence L. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: USMC
- Morrison, David R. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Mathematics and Physics
- Morrow, Sue Ann (Box 39)
- Morton, Michael M. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Germanic Language and Literature
- Moser, Louise (Box 39)
- Moses, Elizabeth (Box 88)
- Moses, Elizabeth (Box 136)
- Moses, Michael (Box 88)
- Moses, Montrose J. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Anatomy, Cell Biology
- Moses, Montrose J. (Box 136)
- Mosley, Albert (Box 88)
- Moss, Florence (Box 88)
- Moss, Florence (Box 136)
- Moss, Florence (Box 153)
- Mosteller, Robert Paul (Box 88)
- Mosteller, Robert Paul (Box 136)
- Moulin, Herve J. (Box 88)
- Mouzon, James Carlisle (Box 136)
- Mouzon, James Carlisle (Box 88)
- Moylan, Joseph A., Jr. (Box 88)
- Moylan, Joseph A., Jr. (Box 136)
- Mudimbe, Valentin (Box 88)
- Mueller, Berndt (Box 88)
- Mueller, Earl George (Box 39)
- Mueller, Julia (Box 39)
- Mueller, Julia (Box 88)
- Mueller, Julia (Box 136)
- Muenzinger, Karl F. (Box 88)
- Muga, Bruce J. (Box 88)
- Muga, Bruce J. (Box 136)
- Muhlbaier, Lawrence H. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biometry and Medical Informatics; Database for Cardiovascular Diseases
- Muhlbaier, Lawrence H. (Box 136)
- Mullen, Kevin E., Trustee 1994-1997 (Box 117)
- Mueller, Berndt (Box 88)
- Muller, William H., Jr., Trustee (Box 117)
- Muller, Yvonne (Box 39)
- Mulligan, Thomas (Box 39)
- Mumford, Lawrence Quincy (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; 11th Librarian of Congress
- Munger, Michael (Box 88)
- Munson, Bruce (Box 88)
- Munson, Bruce (Box 136)
- Munson, Bruce (Box 153)
- Munyan, Merril Calvin (Box 136)
- Munyan, Merril Calvin (Box 88)
- Murch, Arvin (Box 153)
- Murch, Arvin W. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sociology Dept., 1969-
- Murch, Arvin W. (Box 136)
- Murchison, Clint, Jr. (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Financier
- Murphy, Charles (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Undersecretary of Agriculture
- Murphy, Charles S. (Box 136)
- Murphy, Charles S., Trustee (Box 117)
- Murphy, Roland (Box 88)
- Murphy, Roland E. (Box 39)
- Murphy, Roland E. (Box 136)
- Murray, Brad (Box 88)
- Murray, F. J. (Box 88)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, retired 8-31-80